<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivy&#39;s Lore Hoard</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivy&#39;s Lore Hoard</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;This is where you&amp;rsquo;d respond in your head &amp;lsquo;General Kenobi&amp;rsquo;. Yes? No? Ah, alright. I won&amp;rsquo;t hold that against you. As you&amp;rsquo;ve probably already figured out, my name is Ivy. I live in the Seattle area with my family and have been working as a writer for about five years now. I have written and self published two books under a pen name, worked on homebrew D&amp;amp;D campaigns with my friends, and just generally been tinkering in about fifty other projects. Seriously, you should see my desk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/desk/characters/characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/desk/characters/characters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A list of characters I have made for campaigns I have either run myself or have played as. Most come with a background, a description of appearance and some interesting notes or items they have carried/used.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;azaela&#34;&gt;Azaela&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Azaela is a Tiefling who was born blind on the streets of a coastal town. She was abandoned on the steps of an orphanage, but because of her infernal blood she was discarded and left for dead. Despite this, she was taken in by another Tiefling who ran a small thieving operation with others of their kind. She learned to rely on her other senses and became quite the charlatan, alternating between pickpocketing and conning wealthy nobles out of their accessories by hustling them with her blindness. Eventually, she managed to pilfer a ring that housed a genie. In exchange for sight, she promised to fulfill the genie&amp;rsquo;s every wish. As an adult now, she runs a shop that specializes in extravagant and beautiful adventuring gear. Obsessed with all things colorful and shiny, she enjoys making practical adventuring armor and accessories that don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice fashion for usability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you wish to contact me, please slip your info in between the floor boards. Or if you&amp;rsquo;re low on parchment feel free to email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:ivy@lee.social&#34;&gt;ivy@lee.social&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example Flow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/desk/narrative-design/example-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/desk/narrative-design/example-flow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A example of my general work flow for a game.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;high-level-narrative-summary&#34;&gt;High Level Narrative Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zokar is a Myconid with a hunger for power. Above all else, he desires to consume as much power from the world as possible and utilize it to become a new God. Using his strange abilities to grow mushrooms along the surface of the world, he spreads his spores to unsuspecting victims, drawing them to his cause and aiding him in his plans.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones: A Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/game-of-thrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/game-of-thrones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been six years since Game of Thrones ended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jesus Christ.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, let me start by saying Game of Thrones had to have one of the worst endings ever written. Characters made decisions that made no sense for them to make, said things they would never have said in earlier situations, and overall everything just went to absolute shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or did it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yeah, yeah, alright. It was bad. But not for the reasons I once thought. After five years of grieving for muh queen, I have reevaluated my stance on the show and the ending. Now, I come to the people of the realm in the defense of the greatest fantasy show ever made.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Items and Vegetation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/desk/items/items-and-vegetation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/desk/items/items-and-vegetation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A collection of items and plants I have made for various campaigns I have run and novels I have written.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;items&#34;&gt;Items&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;poisoned-gauntlets&#34;&gt;Poisoned Gauntlets&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gauntlets with clawed fingertips that contain a vial of poison in each metal tip. With enough pressure, the poison released through a tiny hole into the victim&amp;rsquo;s skin. Vials contain an intense concentration and only release a few drops into the victim with each attack. Vials do need to be refilled when emptied.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/desk/locations/locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/desk/locations/locations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A list of notable locations I have made for Game Masters to drop into their world. These include a name and layout description, and a few other bits such as economic use, interesting landmarks and notable shops. Any that I&amp;rsquo;ve made for a campaign also include hooks to interest players into sticking around and exploring.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;wedgerock-cove&#34;&gt;Wedgerock Cove&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wedgerock Cove is a bustling trading hub, home to the Fairwind Merchants&amp;rsquo; guild hall—a collective of tradesmen and ship captains dealing in luxury goods like silks, spices, and fine jewels. While most of the coves inhabitants are upstanding citizens, a few crooked merchants have found their way into the guilds officers positions. They now use their influence to smuggle drugs and information hidden among their wares. This has caused an undercurrent of tension among the people of the cove, who can feel the unsavory nature of such deals encroaching on their affluent lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/desk/publications/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/desk/publications/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here you can find a few of my past publicized works.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;journalism&#34;&gt;Journalism&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.archive.org/web/20221203230242/https://staticmagazine.net/twenty-one-pilots-bandito-tour/&#34;&gt;Twenty One Pilots: The Bandito Tour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Published by Static Magazine&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dallasobserver.com/arts/vampire-court-of-dallas-allows-more-than-just-vampires-11079326&#34;&gt;Vampire Court of Dallas Really Just Wants To Help Others&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Published by The Dallas Observer&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;novels&#34;&gt;Novels&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://a.co/d/dhHRVhb&#34;&gt;The Doppelgänger Files&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Published on Amazon in 2017&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://a.co/d/hKKJ3ym&#34;&gt;Haunted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Published on Amazon in 2021&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;game-resources&#34;&gt;Game Resources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dmsguild.com/product/489522/The-Town-of-Motlier?affiliate_id=4377766&#34;&gt;The Town of Motlier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Published on DMs Guild in 2024&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dmsguild.com/product/497847/The-Town-of-Fairhaven&#34;&gt;The Town of Fairhaven&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Published on DMs Guild in 2024&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Races, Creatures, and Classes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/desk/races-creatures-classes/races-creatures-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/desk/races-creatures-classes/races-creatures-classes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here is a list of races and creature types that I&amp;rsquo;ve made for Game Masters to add to their world. Most come with special feats or abilities.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;araquin&#34;&gt;Araquin&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A race of spider creatures, they possess milky white skin covered in fine hairs that can be colored in grey, black, or tan. Some grow hard, black chitin across their torso. They possess two main eyes and two smaller eyes, lidless and mostly black although there have been some known to have jewel toned colors. The females have small mandibles that grow from the side of their mouths and sharp teeth, while the males can possess two to four extra limbs that end in claws instead of hands or feet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last of Us Part II: A Hollow Victory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-last-of-us-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-last-of-us-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s time for season two of The Last of Us and my god have I been vibrating with excitement for this. I decided against replaying the game before it came out, partially to give the writers a chance to impress me, but mostly because I simply do not have that kind of time right now. Either way, as I waited for the first episode to drop I exchanged a stark realization with my husband:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my desk!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/type_index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/type_index/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-desk&#34;&gt;Welcome to my desk!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello there! Welcome to my desk. Please, come in and make yourself at home. Take a seat, have some coffee, and take your time sifting through my desk. I&amp;rsquo;ve got something for everyone. A sample of my &lt;a href=&#34;https://ivylee.weblog.lol/game-works/narrative-design-doc&#34;&gt;workflow&lt;/a&gt; can be found on the top, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ivylee.weblog.lol/game-works/items-and-vegetations&#34;&gt;items&lt;/a&gt; are in the right drawer and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ivylee.weblog.lol/game-works/locations&#34;&gt;locations&lt;/a&gt; in the left. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ivylee.weblog.lol/game-works/characters&#34;&gt;Characters&lt;/a&gt; can be found stuffed into the middle drawer, and various other works are hidden here and there. And if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for me, look no further than the figure spying on you from underneath the floorboards. Yes, those are my eyes blinking between the panels. Don&amp;rsquo;t mind me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Aliens Go?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/where-did-all-the-aliens-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/where-did-all-the-aliens-go/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And why we peaked with Farscape.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, I stubbornly refused to like sci-fi. Space was boring and frankly all the techy stuff made my eyes glaze over. Give me swords and orcs over aliens and space ships any day. Then I watched Star Wars for the first time when I was twenty years old. Rather, my newlywed husband made me watch them all because The Force Awakens was coming out that year and we were going to see it in theaters with his entire friends and family. I relented, with much grumbling and huffing and when the credits rolled on Episode 3, I had lost my ever-loving mind. The lasers! Jabba the Hutt! Han Solo! Stormtroopers! I was absolutely appalled that my uneducated former self had stolen such amazing movies from me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
