<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Ivy&#39;s Lore Hoard</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Ivy&#39;s Lore Hoard</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones: A Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/game-of-thrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/game-of-thrones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been six years since Game of Thrones ended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jesus Christ.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, let me start by saying Game of Thrones had to have one of the worst endings ever written. Characters made decisions that made no sense for them to make, said things they would never have said in earlier situations, and overall everything just went to absolute shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or did it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yeah, yeah, alright. It was bad. But not for the reasons I once thought. After five years of grieving for muh queen, I have reevaluated my stance on the show and the ending. Now, I come to the people of the realm in the defense of the greatest fantasy show ever made.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Last of Us Part II: A Hollow Victory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-last-of-us-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-last-of-us-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s time for season two of The Last of Us and my god have I been vibrating with excitement for this. I decided against replaying the game before it came out, partially to give the writers a chance to impress me, but mostly because I simply do not have that kind of time right now. Either way, as I waited for the first episode to drop I exchanged a stark realization with my husband:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Did All The Aliens Go?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/where-did-all-the-aliens-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/where-did-all-the-aliens-go/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And why we peaked with Farscape.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, I stubbornly refused to like sci-fi. Space was boring and frankly all the techy stuff made my eyes glaze over. Give me swords and orcs over aliens and space ships any day. Then I watched Star Wars for the first time when I was twenty years old. Rather, my newlywed husband made me watch them all because The Force Awakens was coming out that year and we were going to see it in theaters with his entire friends and family. I relented, with much grumbling and huffing and when the credits rolled on Episode 3, I had lost my ever-loving mind. The lasers! Jabba the Hutt! Han Solo! Stormtroopers! I was absolutely appalled that my uneducated former self had stolen such amazing movies from me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
